Kettle and Idol
Now, it's an early reining.
Please be informed from Pannon-chan.
Kyushu Jyoshiryoku 4th album "Universe" will be released.
Thank you very much.
Our 4th album "Universe" is scheduled to be released on July 4.
We are planning to release many more releases in the future,
We hope you will come and play with us.
And what kind of album is it?
This album is inspired by the universe,
The songs are all about planets and the sun,
The songs are all about planets or suns or planets in the universe?
Many of the songs are named after the universe,
I think you will enjoy that aspect of the album.
For example, what kind of universe?
Planet Euphoria,
You are the sun,
You are the sun.
And then there's Starseeker.
It's kind of cosmic.
or Stary Night,
There's a song called "Removal Song",
Removal songs?
This elimination song has a message that you can start over and over again,
Many people have listened to the elimination song and said, "I really like this song,
I've had a lot of people tell me that they really like this song,
It's like a grand cheering up to you all,
I hope that many of you will listen to this song as well.
I see.
There will be many release events for U-NIVERSE,
How will Kamu-chan respond to us at the special event?
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Really?
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
Bye-bye.
Eyeballs with your sister at the back of the brush,
The ball ampoule with Fushikata with the ladle.
Yes.
That's great.
Now, and the album, the new album, what's next?
Yes. And Kyushu Girl's Walk is having regular performances once a month in Fukuoka and Tokyo.
In Fukuoka, we perform at Bayside Live Hall,
And in Tokyo, at Akihabara Culture's Theater,
The show consists of three acts,
The show consists of three acts: Act 1, Act 2, and Act 3,
You can see the different faces of Kyushu Girls Walk in each act.
Just by seeing this regular performance, you can understand everything about the Kyushu Women's Walk,
You will be able to understand everything about the Kyushu Girls Walk just by seeing this regular performance,
If you are interested in Kyushu Girls Walk, please come and join us. We are looking forward to seeing you.
Now, here I am, Akabanehara.
May I offer Lolo a cup of tea?
Yes.
Today's tea is jasmine tea.
Jasmine tea.
Yes.
Looks delicious.
Do you usually drink tea?
Yes, I do. I love it.
I hope I don't spill it.
Don't you have to spray something?
Oh, but please say a little more.
I'm not sure which way things are going to go.
I'd like to see what will happen.
Can I tell you that I'm not allowed to say that?
Yes, please go ahead. Please drink normally.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Delicious.
Is it good?
It will taste even better if you drink it with Japanese sweets or other snacks.
It is very tasty.
It warms me up.
Do you have any last words?
Yes, I do.
I would like to show Kyushu Jyoshiryoku to as many people as possible at the Tokyo Yakan Land.
If you are interested in my performance at Tokyo Yakan Land, please come to Kyushu Jyoshiryoku's live show as well.
It's wonderful.
It's really good.
Thank you very much.
I think we need to learn from you and your staff, don't we?
Now, may I ask you to look at the camera as we say goodbye?
Yes.
See you soon!
Bye bye!
You can come visit us in Fukuoka.
Nighttime Island Idol
This program is
Momoga-chan
Teramii-san
Kazuku
Robin Cop
This program was provided by Mr. Roberto.
Thank you for the offer!